Finding aid for the R.B. Kitaj papers LSC.1741
UCLA Library Special Collections
- 9. Business Correspondence, 1961-2007; 19 boxes
  - No Subseries assigned
    - LA Louver Gallery, 1984 - 2005; 22 items. (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Los Angeles County Museum of Art (LACMA), 1993 - 2006; 70 items. (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Magazines/Newspapers/Freelance Journalists, ca. 1984 May 14 - 2005 December 13; 44 items. (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Mahoney, James, ca. 1984 June 4 - 2003 January 15; 45 items. (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Marlborough Gallery and Marlborough Fine Art Ltd., ca. 1985 April 17 - 2005 June 22; 51 items. (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - Metropolitan Museum of Art (MET), 1975 - 2005; 10 items. (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Mitchell-Innes & Nash Gallery, 1997 December 1 - 2001 January 23; 3 items. (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Modern Art Museum of Fort Worth, 1991 October 1 - 1995 February 17; 3 items. (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Modern Painter Magazine, 1991 - 2002; 10 items. (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Museo de Bellas, Artes de Bilbao, 2003 March 31 - 2005 September 27; 11 items. (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - Museo de la Solidaridad Salvador Allende, 1992 June 4 - 1993 April 27; 4 items. (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - Museo Nacional Centro de Arte Reina Sofia, 1998 March 2 - 1998 March 16; 3 items. (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - Museum of Contemporary Art (MOCA), 1967 - 2003; 8 items. (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - Museum of Fine Arts (MFA), 2004 - 2006; 4 items. (Box 33, Folder 29)
    - Museum of Modern Art (MoMA), 1975 - 2006; 10 items. (Box 33, Folder 30)
    - Museum of Modern Art, Oxford, 1984 September 14 - 2001 January 11; 3 items. (Box 33, Folder 31)
    - Naropa Institute, ca. 1990 December 18 - 1997 September 6; 7 items. (Box 33, Folder 32)
    - National Academy of Design, 1996 May 30 - 2004 June 22; 7 items. (Box 33, Folder 33)
    - National Campaign for the Arts, 1998 March 31 - 2000 December 1; 5 items. (Box 33, Folder 34)
    - National Endowment for the Arts, 1984 August 1 - 1984 October 16; 3 items. (Box 33, Folder 35)
    - National Foundation for Jewish Culture, 1987 - 2006; 18 items. (Box 33, Folder 36)
    - National Gallery of Australia (NGA), 1985 - 2004; 21 items. (Box 33, Folder 37)
    - National Gallery (1 of 2), 1993 - 2007; 42 items. (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - National Gallery (2 of 2), 2000 - 2002; 55 items. (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - British Library National Sound Archive, 1997 May 27; 4 items. (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - National Museum of Wales - Nowikovsky, Karin, ca. 1985 December 20 - 2004 May 12; 16 items. (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - National Portrait Gallery, 1986 - 2006; 12 items. (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - New Republic Magazine, 1992 October 5 - 1999 January 18; 3 items. (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - New York Academy of Art, 2000 - 2001; 3 items. (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - New York Arts Magazine, ca. 1998 December - 1999 May 5; 4 items. (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - New York Graphic Society Books, 1985 April 4 - 1985 September 4; 5 items. (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - New York Studio School of Drawing, Painting and Sculpture, 1998 - 2006; 21 items. (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Northern Centre for Contemporary Art, 1996 January 19 - 1996 January 29; 2 items. (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Odyssia Gallery - Oxford Jewish Congregation, 4 items. (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Old Vic Theatre, 1985 August 29 - 1986 January 13; 6 items. (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Oxford University Press, 1998 February 23; 2 items. (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Painting loans materials, 1994 -1996; 35 items. (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Pallant House Gallery and Trust, ca. 1997 January 3 - 2005 March 9; 42 items. (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Patrice, Kerin - Posen, Felix, ca. 1982 February 20 - 2000 October 31; 16 items. (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Peer Introduction (A - M), ca. 1984 July 27 - 2006 May 19; 76 items. (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Peer Introduction (N - Z), ca. 1985 - 2005 May 19; 103 items. (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Pennsylvania Academy of Fine Arts, 2001 - 2005; 14 items. (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Photographers/Filmmakers, 1984 November 12 - 2004 May 19; 19 items. (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Prints and lithographs correspondence, 1987 - 1992; 28 items. (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Property/Investments, ca. 1992 May 5 - 2005 September 14; 29 items. (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Publishers and Contribution Requests (A - M), ca. 1985 April 24 - 2006 February 17; 109 items. (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Publishers and Contribution Requests (N - Z), ca. 1983 November 9 - 2005 January 14; 53 items. (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Rainer, Dachine - Rutberg, Jack, ca. 1984 August 16 - 2005 April 29; 24 items. (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Royal Academy of Arts, ca. 1984 May 10 - 2005 May 26; 125 items. (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Royal College of Art, ca. 1984 July 3 - 2006 May 17; 70 items. (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Charles Russell Solicitors, 1996 April 3 - 1996 November 14; 4 items. (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Salander-O'Reilly Galleries - Szarkowski, John, ca. 1984 July 6 - 2005 April 1; 39 items. (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Serpentine Gallery -- London, 1984 July 4 - 1999 April; 4 items. (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Skirball mural materials, 1994 - 1995; 20 items. (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Skowhegan School of Painting and Sculpture, 1984 - 1985; 8 items. (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Smithsonian Institution, 1985 - 2005; 6 items. (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Sotheby's, 1972 - 1997; 10 items. (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Spertus Institute of Jewish Studies, 1999 - 1999; 13 items. (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Sprengel Museum Hannover, 1998; 8 items. (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Staff Notes To/From Kitaj, 1988; 15 items. (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Student Introductions and Requests, 1984 - 2005; 134 items. (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Sujo Gallery, 1998 - 1998; 5 items. (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Tanner, Marcia - Tucker, Sam, ca. 1985 February 15 - 2005 March 9; 13 items. (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Tate Art Magazine and Publishing, ca. 1985 November 14 - 2002 July 17; 16 items. (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Tate Gallery, Liverpool, 1993 December 9 - 1995 November 21; 2 items. (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Tate Gallery, London, 1976 - 2004; 62 items. (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Taxes, 1998 January 12 - 2000 October 19; 2 items. (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Television Networks and Program Requests, 1985 October 15 - 1997 May 9; 6 items. (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Times, London, 1995 December 6 - 1998 August 5; 3 items. (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Turning Point School Fundraising, ca. 1998 March - 2006 June 13; 15 items. (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - U.S. Art Company, Inc. - University of the Arts, Philadelphia, ca. 1985 June 3 - 2004 October 14; 20 items. (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Universities/Colleges (assorted), ca. 1984 October 18 - 2000 July 10; 42 items. (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - University of California Press, 12 items. (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - University of Durham, 1995 July 7 - 2004 September 7; 19 items. (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - University of Oxford, Ashmolean Museum, 2002 May 22 - 2002 August 20; 3 items. (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - Vancouver, City of - Vermont Studio Center, 1994 March 24 - 2006 January 17; 6 items. (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - Waddington Galleries, Ltd. - Wyner, Trudy, 1985 - 1998; 24 items. (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - Weizmann Institute of Science, 1994 January 20; 2 items. (Box 36, Folder 24)
    - Westminster Synagogue, 1992 - 1997; 11 items. (Box 36, Folder 25)
    - Whitney Museum, 1967 - 2003; 9 items. (Box 36, Folder 26)
    - Yad Vashem - Zwemmer Ltd., Art Booksellers, 1984 - 2004; 12 items. (Box 36, Folder 27)
    - Yale Center for British Art, 1985 - 2005; 7 items. (Box 36, Folder 28)
    - Yeshiva University Museum, 2001 - 2003; 6 items. (Box 36, Folder 29)
    - House lease and sale materials, 1969 - 1972; 50 items. (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - House sale materials, 1957 -1967; 20 items. (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Housing materials (1 of 5), 1971 -1973; 80 items. (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Housing materials (4 of 5), 1987; 20 items. (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Brighton, Andrew, 1985; 35 items. (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Fuller, Peter, undated; 1 item. (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - Hyman, Timothy, 1985; 24 items. (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - Podro, Michael, undated; 6 items. (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - Ackerman, Martin, 1976 - 1987; 14 items. (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - ANC [African National Congress], 1979; 4 items. (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Air & Space (Art Services Grants Ltd), 1980; 4 items. (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Akron Art Institute, 1971; 4 items. (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Albright-Knox Art Gallery, 1976 - 1993; 4 items. (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Aleph Society Inc., 1996, 1998; 5 items. (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - American References, 1989 - 1990; 6 items. (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - American School in London, 1970 - 1979; 4 items. (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Amnesty International, 1975 - 1990; 15 items. (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Angela Flowers Gallery, 1980 - 1984; 4 items. (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Arion Press, 1983 - 2007; 25 items. (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - Art and Artists magazine, 1966 - 1969; 3 items. (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - Art & Design, 1988 - 1992; 12 items. (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - Art Appeal: Defense and Aid Fund (for South Africa) Ltd, 1981 - 1985; 10 items. (Box 63, Folder 14)
    - Art for McGovern, 1972; 5 items. (Box 63, Folder 15)
    - Artforum, 5 items. (Box 63, Folder 16)
    - Artists against the War in Vietnam, 1967 - 1968; 8 items. (Box 63, Folder 17)
    - Artists for Nuclear Disarmament at the ACME Gallery, 1981 - 1991; 7 items. (Box 63, Folder 18)
    - Artist's Postcards, 1978; 6 items. (Box 63, Folder 19)
    - Artlaw Services Ltd, 1981; 4 items. (Box 63, Folder 20)
    - Artlog, no date; 2 items. (Box 63, Folder 21)
    - Artnews, 1993 - 1998; 3 items. (Box 63, Folder 22)
    - The Art Newspaper, 1991 - 1994; 5 items. (Box 63, Folder 23)
    - Art Review, 1993; 2 items. (Box 63, Folder 24)
    - Art Strike, 1968 - 1970; 4 items. (Box 63, Folder 25)
    - Arts Council (1 of 4), 1960 - 1975; 64 items. (Box 63, Folder 26)
    - Arts Council (2 of 4), 1976 - 1979; 50 items. (Box 63, Folder 27)
    - Arts Council (3 of 4), 1980 - 1997; 40 items. (Box 63, Folder 28)
    - Arts Council (4 of 4), 1975 - 1977; 21 items. (Box 63, Folder 28)
    - Artscribe, no date; 4 items. (Box 63, Folder 29)
    - Art Site Gallery -- Bath Festival, 1986 - 1989; 19 items. (Box 63, Folder 30)
    - Ashmolean Museum, 1990; 1 item. (Box 63, Folder 31)
    - Astrup Fearnley Museum, 1993 - 1998; 5 items. (Box 63, Folder 32)
    - Australian National Gallery, 1988 - 1990; 5 items. (Box 63, Folder 33)
    - Badischer Kunstverein, 1969 - 1970; 2 items. (Box 63, Folder 34)
    - Baltimore Museum of Art, 1977 - 1989; 6 items. (Box 63, Folder 35)
    - Barbican Art Gallery, 1990; 6 items. (Box 63, Folder 36)
    - Basil Blackwell Publishers, 1980 - 1987; 10 items. (Box 63, Folder 37)
    - Belgische Radio, 1982; 4 items. (Box 63, Folder 38)
    - Ben Uri Art Society, 1987 - 2007; 11 items. (Box 63, Folder 39)
    - Bertram Rota Booksellers, 1964 - 1981; 25 items. (Box 63, Folder 40)
    - Roger Bevan: The New Academy for Art Studies, 1990 - 1993; 5 items. (Box 63, Folder 41)
    - Bezalel Academy of Arts and Design -- Jerusalem, 1974 - 1986; 7 items. (Box 63, Folder 42)
    - Bibliothèque Nacionale de France, 1973; 1 item. (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Biennale of Sydney, 1985 - 1986; 4 items. (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Bijutsu Shuppan-sha, 1965 - 1969; 5 items. (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Birthright, 1988; 2 items. (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Black Sparrow Press, 1970 - 1984; 24 items. (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Bohm-Duchen, Monica, 1991 - 1996; 13 items. (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Bookdealers -- Various, 1964 - 1990; 76 items. (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Boymans Museum -- Rotterdam, 1970, 1976; 2 items. (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - BBC [British Broadcasting Corporation], 1963 - 1996; 15 items. (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - British Council, 1963 - 2007; 70 items. (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - British Embassy, 1978; 1 item. (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - British Film Institute, 1990 - 1994; 12 items. (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - British International Print Biennale, 1968 - 1986; 11 items. (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - The British Library, 1990 - 2005; 5 items. (Box 64, Folder 14)
    - The British Museum, 1979 - 1994; 7 items. (Box 64, Folder 15)
    - The British School at Rome, 1961 - 1974; 34 items. (Box 64, Folder 16)
    - The British School at Rome: Meeting Minutes, 1965 - 1973; 15 items. (Box 64, Folder 17)
    - The Brooklyn Museum, 1972 - 1980; 5 items. (Box 64, Folder 18)
    - The Burlington Magazine, 1987 - 1986; 5 items. (Box 64, Folder 19)
    - California College of Arts and Crafts, 1970 - 1995; 13 items. (Box 64, Folder 20)
    - Camberwell School of Arts and Crafts, 1961 - 1965; 4 items. (Box 64, Folder 21)
    - Cambridge University Press, 1967 - 1985; 19 items. (Box 64, Folder 22)
    - Canadian Centre for Architecture, 1996; 4 items. (Box 64, Folder 23)
    - Cape Goliard Press, 1967 - 1968; 5 items. (Box 64, Folder 24)
    - Cartwright Hall, 1978; 1 item. (Box 64, Folder 25)
    - Centre Georges Pompidou, 1977, 1999; 5 items. (Box 64, Folder 26)
    - Charles of the Ritz, 1983; 10 items. (Box 64, Folder 27)
    - Chelsea Rare Books, 1984 - 1988; 10 items. (Box 64, Folder 28)
    - Chelsea School of Art, 1962 - 1981; 8 items. (Box 64, Folder 29)
    - Chile Solidarity, 1974 - 1983; 9 items. (Box 64, Folder 30)
    - Cincinnati Art Museum, 1966 - 1973; 40 items. (Box 64, Folder 31)
    - City of Lights, no date; 1 item. (Box 64, Folder 32)
    - City of Sheffield Art Galleries, 1964 - 1990; 11 items. (Box 64, Folder 33)
    - Cleveland Museum of Art, 1966 - 2000; 45 items. (Box 64, Folder 34)
    - Conjuctions Literary Magazine, 1983 - 1985; 5 items. (Box 64, Folder 35)
    - Columbia University, 1995 - 2002; 2 items. (Box 64, Folder 36)
    - Columbus Museum of Art, 1982; 8 items. (Box 64, Folder 37)
    - Committee of Artists Against Apartheid, 1981 - 1982; 9 items. (Box 64, Folder 38)
    - Container Corporation of America, 1967 - 1980; 7 items. (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - The Contemporary Art Society, 1962; 2 items. (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Cooper Union, 1966 - 2007; 27 items. (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Corner Udstilling, 2002; 2 items. (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Council for National Academic Awards, 1975; 4 items. (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - County of Cleveland, 1979 - 1982; 5 items. (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Crusaid, 1988; 5 items. (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Danish-Israel Cultural Committee, 1975; 3 items. (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - David Hockney Retrospective, 1988 - 1993; 10 items. (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Dartmouth College, 1977 - 1984; 13 items. (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Deborah Rogers Ltd, 1987; 3 items. (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Debrett's Distinguished People of Today, 1988 - 2007; 18 items. (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - Deutscher Akademischer Austauschdienst, 1969, 1979; 6 items. (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Documenta Kassel, 1968, 1977; 4 items. (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - Double Elephant Press, 1973; 2 items. (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - Durham University, 1989, 2007; 7 items. (Box 65, Folder 16)
    - Edition Olympia 1972, 1969 - 1973; 23 items. (Box 65, Folder 17)
    - Embassy of the United States, 1966 - 1997; 9 items. (Box 65, Folder 18)
    - Enitharmon Press, 1991 - 2005; 17 items. (Box 65, Folder 19)
    - The Eye Gallery, 1990; 10 items. (Box 65, Folder 20)
    - Fan Mail (A- J), 1967 - 1990; 61 items. (Box 65, Folder 21)
    - Fan Mail (K - Z), 1970 - 2006; 59 items. (Box 65, Folder 22)
    - Federated Union of Black Arts [FUBA], 1983; 2 items. (Box 65, Folder 23)
    - Fisher Fine Art Limited: London, 1970 - 1993; 13 items. (Box 65, Folder 24)
    - Fulcrum Press, 1966, 1969; 2 items. (Box 65, Folder 25)
    - Galeria Cadaques, 1977 - 1979; 9 items. (Box 65, Folder 26)
    - Galerie Claude Bernard, 1973 - 1983; 10 items. (Box 65, Folder 27)
    - Galerie d'eendt nv, 1967 - 1968; 5 items. (Box 65, Folder 28)
    - Galerie Dorothea Leonhart, 1970 - 1971; 6 items. (Box 65, Folder 29)
    - Galerie Mikro, 1969 - 1970; 9 items. (Box 65, Folder 30)
    - Galleria Odyssia, 1968 - 1978; 7 items. (Box 65, Folder 31)
    - Galleri Haaken, 1979 - 1982; 5 items. (Box 65, Folder 32)
    - Gay Men's Health Crisis, 1982, 1988; 2 items. (Box 65, Folder 33)
    - Gemini G.E.L., 1971 - 2000; 4 items. (Box 65, Folder 34)
    - Gilman, Sander, 1995 - 2006; 5 items. (Box 65, Folder 35)
    - Glasgow Museums & Art Galleries, 1989 - 1990; 4 items. (Box 65, Folder 36)
    - Glasgow School of Art, 1977 - 1978; 7 items. (Box 65, Folder 37)
    - Goliard Press, 1966; 2 items. (Box 65, Folder 38)
    - The Grenfell Press, 1984 - 1985; 17 items. (Box 65, Folder 39)
    - Guggenheim Museum, 1980 - 1990; 5 items. (Box 65, Folder 40)
    - Hamburger Kunsthalle, 1984 - 1996; 8 items. (Box 65, Folder 41)
    - Hamish Hamilton, 1991 - 1994; 16 items. (Box 65, Folder 42)
    - Hank Baum, 1974 - 1976; 5 items. (Box 65, Folder 43)
    - The Hayward Gallery, 1974 - 1996; 6 items. (Box 65, Folder 44)
    - The Hebrew University of Jerusalem, 1986 - 1994; 13 items. (Box 65, Folder 45)
    - Heydons, 1994 - 2000; 5 items. (Box 65, Folder 46)
    - Hirshhorn Museum, 1977 - 1994; 43 items. (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Hochschule für Bildende Kunste Hamburg, 1979; 10 items. (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - House, Gordon, 1970 - 1977; 10 items. (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Hornsey College of Art, 1969 - 1991; 5 items. (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Hunterian Art Gallery (University of Glasgow), 1980 - 1981; 7 items. (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Ikon Gallery, 1977; 5 items. (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - The Independent, 1988 - 1992; 4 items. (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Institute of Contemporary Arts, 1961 - 1989; 30 items. (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - International Biennial Exhibition in Tokyo, 1966 - 1974; 6 items. (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - The Israel Museum, 1966 - 1993; 33 items. (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - James Hyman Fine Art, 2005 - 2007; 7 items. (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - James Kirkman Ltd, 1977 - 1994; 8 items. (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - Janie C. Lee Gallery, 1987 - 1990; 4 items. (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - The Jewish Chronicle, 1990 - 1994; 3 items. (Box 66, Folder 14)
    - The Jewish Museum -- New York, 1982 - 2007; 21 items. (Box 66, Folder 15)
    - The Jewish Student Arts Festival, 1991; 4 items. (Box 66, Folder 16)
    - The John and Mable Ringling Museum of Art, 1983 - 1984; 6 items. (Box 66, Folder 17)
    - Jonathan Cape Limited, 1969 - 2000; 12 items. (Box 66, Folder 18)
    - JP Morgan, 1996 - 2005; 6 items. (Box 66, Folder 19)
    - Jüdisches Museum Wien [Jewish Museum, Vienna], 1994 - 1998; 7 items. (Box 66, Folder 20)
    - KCET, 1970; 4 items. (Box 66, Folder 21)
    - Kelpra Studio Ltd, 1967 - 1989; 22 items. (Box 66, Folder 22)
    - Kent State University, 1971 - 1982; 13 items. (Box 66, Folder 23)
    - Kestner-Geellschaft e.V., 1970 - 1983; 9 items. (Box 66, Folder 24)
    - Kunsthalle Basel, 1968; 1 item. (Box 66, Folder 25)
    - Kunstnernes Hus, 1982, 1987; 2 items. (Box 66, Folder 26)
    - L.A. Louver, 1979 - 2005; 40 items. (Box 66, Folder 27)
    - L.A. Wallrich Books, 1974 - 1976; 6 items. (Box 66, Folder 28)
    - Leeds University Union, 1965 - 1977; 7 items. (Box 66, Folder 29)
    - Lefevre Gallery, 1982 - 1993; 8 items. (Box 66, Folder 30)
    - The Liberal Jewish Synagogue, 1988 - 1989; 8 items. (Box 66, Folder 31)
    - Livingstone, Marco, 1976 - 1993; 22 items. (Box 66, Folder 32)
    - Lloyds Bank Ltd, 1966 - 1987; 9 items. (Box 66, Folder 33)
    - Lockheed, 1968 - 1969; 5 items. (Box 66, Folder 34)
    - The London Group, 1978; 1 item. (Box 66, Folder 35)
    - London Lighthouse, 1988, 1990; 4 items. (Box 66, Folder 36)
    - London Review of Books, 1979 - 1992; 8 items. (Box 66, Folder 37)
    - London Underground, 1990 - 1993; 8 items. (Box 66, Folder 38)
    - LACMA [Los Angeles County Museum of Art], 1965 - 2007; 82 items. (Box 66, Folder 39)
    - Louville, Francois, 1983; 3 items. (Box 66, Folder 40)
    - Marion Boyars Publishers Ltd, 1983 - 1993; 5 items. (Box 66, Folder 41)
    - Market Nursery, 1976; 4 items. (Box 66, Folder 42)
    - Marlborough (1 of 6), 1962 - 1966; 68 items. (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Marlborough (2 of 6), 1967 - 1969; 88 items. (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Marlborough (3 of 6), 1970 - 1979; 80 items. (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Marlborough (4 of 6), 1980 - 1989; 86 items. (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Marlborough (5 of 6), 1990 - 1995; 87 items. (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Marlborough (6 of 6), 1996 - 2007; 73 items. (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Marlborough -- Accounts (1 of 3), 1970 - 1980; 45 items. (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Marlborough -- Accounts (2 of 3), 1980 - 1985; 42 items. (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Marlborough -- Accounts (3 of 3), 1985 - 1987; 17 items. (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Marlborough -- Contracts, 1970 - 1979; 16 items. (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Marlborough -- Exhibit, 1994 - 1999; 18 items. (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Medical Aid for Vietnam, 1967 - 1972; 8 items. (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Melton Research Center, 1981 - 1982; 2 items. (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - The Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1970 - 1995; 21 items. (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Midland Group, 1968 - 1977; 20 items. (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Mishkenot Sha'anamin, 1975 - 1991; 8 items. (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Mitchell Beazley Publishers Ltd, 1980 - 1981; 5 items. (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Modern Painters: Quarterly Journal, 1986 - 1991; 12 items. (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Museum of Autographs, 1981; 1 item. (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - The Museum of Modern Art, 1965 - 2006; 35 items. (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Museum of Modern Art -- Oxford, 1966 - 1990; 18 items. (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - The Museum of Modern Art -- Toyama, 1980 - 1981; 8 items. (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - National Academy of Design, 1980 - 2007; 12 items. (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - National Council for Diplomas in Art and Design, 1965 - 1966; 3 items. (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - National Foundation for Jewish Culture, 1982 - 2005; 20 items. (Box 68, Folder 16)
    - Nationalgalerie, 1968 - 1976; 9 items. (Box 68, Folder 17)
    - National Gallery of Art -- Washington D.C., 1995 - 2001; 3 items. (Box 68, Folder 18)
    - The National Gallery -- London, 1973 - 2002; 39 items. (Box 68, Folder 19)
    - National Gallery of Australia, 1992 - 2007; 7 items. (Box 68, Folder 20)
    - National Gallery of Ireland, 1991; 3 items. (Box 68, Folder 21)
    - National Museum of Wales Cardiff, 1979 - 1980; 2 items. (Box 68, Folder 22)
    - National Portrait Gallery, 1977 - 2007; 9 items. (Box 68, Folder 23)
    - New 57 Gallery, 1975; 10 items. (Box 68, Folder 24)
    - New Contemporaries, 1981, 1986; 3 items. (Box 68, Folder 25)
    - The New Republic, 1992 - 2007; 16 items. (Box 68, Folder 26)
    - The New Yorker, 1977 - 1995; 4 items. (Box 68, Folder 27)
    - New Yorker Graphic Society, 1983; 4 items. (Box 68, Folder 28)
    - New York Times, no date; 1 item. (Box 68, Folder 29)
    - Norwich School of Art, 1985, 1988; 5 items. (Box 68, Folder 30)
    - Nueberger Museum, 1977 - 1978; 3 items. (Box 68, Folder 31)
    - Oberlin College, 1974 - 1975; 8 items. (Box 68, Folder 32)
    - Odyssia Gallery, 1979 - 1981; 14 items. (Box 68, Folder 33)
    - Ohio State: Department of Commerce, 1971; 3 items. (Box 68, Folder 34)
    - The Old Vic Theater, 1984 - 1986; 5 items. (Box 68, Folder 35)
    - Oxford University Press, 1964 - 1987; 22 items. (Box 68, Folder 36)
    - Palm Tree Editions, 1981 - 1982; 11 items. (Box 68, Folder 37)
    - Parnassus: Poetry in Review, 1974 - 1982; 6 items. (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Patricof, Alan, 1969 - 1977; 8 items. (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Paws LA, 1999 - 2000; 5 items. (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Penguin Books, 1966 - 1969; 6 items. (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Permanent Press, 1979 - 1980; 4 items. (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Petersburg Press Ltd, 1971 - 1982; 12 items. (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Peter Stuyvesant Foundation, 1967 - 1981; 6 items. (Box 69, Folder 7)